hello everyone welcome back this is
Richard with hydrogen technology today
with you again and the HT 7 hydrogen
only fuel cell this is more of a
separation demonstration several people
have you know asked about the previous
video and was it really hydrogen coming
out one side was it really oxygen coming
out the other this is a very clear
demonstration right now this line right
here is oxygen and this slide the black
line is the hydrogen we are running only
at around five amps let me pull this
light down so you can see that a little
better that's five amps of power I'm
going to go ahead and crank it up to
about 15 amps so you can get a better
better look at the at the output at 15
amps here we go
now we're running around 15 amps you can
see the hydrogen output is increased
incredibly the oxygen out foot there
again has increased go ahead and do the
lighter demonstration as I did before
this is the oxygen side coming out of
the HT 7 what you're hearing is the
oxygen feeding the flame that's it
you're hearing the oxygen gasp into the
open flame just like feeding a fireplace
more air the the flame likes that air
now we're going to go ahead and show you
the hydrogen side very clear
there you go the HT 7